# Examples for Fitness Coach Assistant

Create a plan and a final fitness guide using the two-stage prompt chaining.

Example 1: Beginner bodyweight program
I want a beginner-friendly 4-week bodyweight program to build strength and endurance. 3 sessions per week. No equipment.

Example 2: 8-week run training
I want to go from no running to completing a 5K in 8 weeks. Time available: 4 days/week. Goal: finish 5K without stopping.

Example 3: Quick office mobility routine
Create a 10-minute mobility and stretching routine suitable for desk workers to do twice daily.

# Example CLI commands:
# python app.py --prompt "Beginner 4-week bodyweight program, 3x/week" --temperature 0.7
# python app.py --prompt "8-week plan to run 5K, 4 days/week" --max_tokens 3000